hypertext markup language or html is a language that defines the structure of
超文本标记语言或 html 是一种定义网页内容结构的语言，
content on a webpage development started in 1989 at cern by tim berners-lee who
由 tim berners-lee 于 1989 年在欧洲核子研究中心开始开发，
had just invented the world's first web browser world wide web the origin of www
他刚刚发明了世界上第一个网络浏览器万维网 www 的起源，
but he needed a publishing language to display content within it so he chose a
但他需要一种发布语言 为了在其中显示内容，因此他选择了一种
syntax based on the standard generalized markup language which uses opening and
基于标准通用标记语言的语法，该语言使用开始和
closing tags to provide meaning to otherwise unorganized text like h4
结束标记为其他无组织的文本提供意义，例如 h4
heading p for paragraph and most importantly a for anchor to link to a
标题 p 用于段落，最重要的是 a 用于链接到
different web page the language underwent many changes during the
不同网页的锚点 语言
initial rise of the internet and was standardized as html5 in 2008 the
在互联网最初兴起期间经历了许多变化，并在 2008 年被标准化为 html5
version we know and love today modern html contains tags to handle a variety
我们今天所知道和喜爱的版本现代html 包含处理
of different media types like video audio and canvas to draw custom graphics
各种不同媒体类型的标签，如视频音频和画布以动态绘制自定义
on the fly the typical html element starts with an opening and closing tag
图形 典型的 html 元素以中间的开始和结束标记开始，
in the middle we have content which might be text or additional html
我们的内容可能是文本或附加 html
elements called children the opening tag may also have one or more attributes
称为子元素的元素 开始标签也可能有一个或多个属性
which are key value pairs that can customize the appearance or behavior of
，这些属性是键值对，可以自定义元素的外观或
the element to build your first web page create a file named index.html this file
行为以构建您的第一个网页创建一个名为 index.html 的文件 此文件
contains a hierarchy of nodes based on the document object model or dom a
包含基于节点的层次结构文档对象模型或 dom
webpage starts with an html tag and has exactly two children a head and a body
网页以 html 标记开始，并且正好有两个子项：头部和
the head contains things that aren't directly shown in the webpage like a
主体头部包含网页中未直接显示的内容，例如
title or a meta tag to give the page a description but notice how the meta
标题或元标记，用于为页面提供描述，但 注意 meta
element has no closing tag closing tags are generally optional when an element
元素是如何没有结束标签的当元素完全独立时，结束标签通常是可选
is fully self-contained the body contains the actual ui for the end user
的 正文包含最终用户的实际 ui
we might start with an h1 heading followed by a paragraph of content to
我们可能以 h1 标题开头，然后是一段内容来
add an image we use an image tag which you'll notice is self-closing then
添加图像 使用一个你会发现它是自动关闭的图像标签，然后
define the source attribute as the file path to the image and you'll want to
将源属性定义为图像的文件路径，你需要
give it an old description to make it accessible to robots and screen readers
给它一个旧的描述，以便机器人可以访问它， 屏幕
what makes web pages revolutionary though is their ability to link to other
阅读器使网页具有革命性的原因在于它们能够链接到
web pages on the information super highway use an anchor tag to create a
信息高速公路上的其他网页使用锚标记创建
link then define the href attributes as the webpage that you want to navigate to
链接，然后将 href 属性定义为
when clicked html also provides structural tags like division or div
单击时要导航到的网页 html 还提供结构 像 Division 或 div
which are often used to group elements together where they can be styled to
这样的标签通常用于将元素组合在一起，当您对代码感到满意时，它们可以被设置为
represent complex ui elements like navbars when you're happy with your code
表示复杂的 ui 元素（如导航栏）
grab the full file path to the html file and paste it into any web browser
获取 html 文件的完整文件路径并将其粘贴到任何 Web 浏览器中
congratulations you just built your first website this has been hypertext
恭喜 你刚刚建立了你的第一个网站 这是超文本
markup language in 100 seconds hit the subscribe button so you don't miss the
标记语言在 100 秒内点击订阅按钮所以你不会错过
upcoming sequels thanks for watching and i will see you in the next one
即将到来的续集 感谢观看，我会在下一个看到你